the bigger the context window the more
chance there is for an llm to get
confused yeah and I found that we have
been binocul against that by breaking
our prompts up instead of populating the
context this way you've said I'm going
to provide you this material it knows
it's expecting that material and by the
time it reads it it knows what to do so
when it comes to Specs like again
canonical specs to us that means that
pieces of a spec like directly relate to
a deterministic behavior that we can
count on talk about the steps that leads
up into task framing it's born out of me
bangging my head against the wall a
specific problem and I was trying to get
llms to make me certain utility
libraries like just certain functions
without using any external dependencies
you're listening to the AI native Dev
brought to you by
[Applause]
[Music]
Tesla on today's episode of the AI
native Dev we're going to be talking all
things prompting and uh why it's one of
the most important things that we need
to think about when dealing with AIS and
llms in our applications uh joining me
today Macy Baker Community engineer at
tessle welcome Macy thank you so much
Simon happy to be here why don't we kick
off with what that means what do you do
at tessla what's your role yeah I think
we're still figuring that out Community
engineer is a bit of a unique job title
especially since we don't have a product
that's out there yet and we have the
very beginnings of a community
effectively I'm working on the AI
engineering team I'm really in the weeds
with these llms and trying to get them
to behave and hopefully once we launch
I'll be talking to other people about
how they are able to make our product
work absolutely and you're always in the
the community the Discord community of
I've seen lots of chats and sharing of
knowledge about that in the Discord
community so for for those listening do
jump into the Discord community and have
Jo and argue with me I would love
yeah so prompting everyone always says
prompting is super important and I think
I hear two things as the cheapest ways
of improving your interactions with an
nlm prompting is one context is the
other why should people go for prompting
first prompting effectively is the
interface to an llm and I think people
really discount how important it is I
know there's a lot of talk about
prompting and how to get the most out of
your prompts but really this is the only
way that we have to truly interact with
the LM and there are conversations about
fine-tuning versus prompting in my mind
like this is the cheapest as you said
it's the cheapest way to get the most
out of your llm also prompts are
disposable like they're living artifacts
they can evolve with you with your
expectations with your product with
whatever it is that you're trying to do
whereas an approach like fine-tuning
might I don't know pin you to to a
certain version of your own that's
really interesting actually because we
were talking with Simon last co-founder
a notion um and he was talking about how
his team actually moving away from the
fine tuning aspect or rather probably I
would say investing far less in the fine
tuning just because as models change and
LS get better the value drops in that
fine tuning I guess that's one thing
that prompting probably stays quite
consistent on is it consistent across
models versions of models will you tend
to get similar results with some of the
tricks that we'll talk about today
that's a really good question I think it
does vary first of all like across
models I think we can bet on llms
getting better yeah I think we can bet
on them improving at the rate the
timeline who knows but they are getting
better all the time and I've noticed
this kind of subjectively and
objectively in our evals with even 40
has improved recently in terms of cross
model prompting tips I think this is so
interesting because this is take chat
GPT and Claude for example this is proof
positive that prompting is so important
I really don't know if they're terribly
different capability wise these models
but a lot of people like this may change
in a matter of weeks at this point but a
lot of people prefer Claude for a lot of
tasks they find it like easier to talk
to they find it understands them better
and if you look at Claud system prompt
tells it to have a little bit more of a
personality I think this comes out
Claude is more opinionated than GPT
Claude is going to have stronger
feelings about what it is that you're
trying to do it's going to make better
assumptions in general and I think if
you read through it system prompt you
can understand why that is because it's
really being guided towards that sort of
affect chat GPT is much
less happy to make assumptions about
what you want much less opinionated in
general yeah I think that's really
interesting now of course the apis uh
from anthropic and open AI don't
necessarily conform to the same system
prompts but I think it's just it's proof
positive how impactful a prompt can be
and that's interesting actually because
on top of that obviously the system
prompt on top of that then we have our
user prompts and noticing those subtle
differences in how they will react so in
your experience Claude being more
opinionated uh and almost more
personable right from the sound of it
yeah my mate yeah that are you sending a
Christmas card to to it might actually
change the way you might prompt
differently on open AI to be more
opinionated if that's what you want or
even on CLA to be less opinionated if
you want that similar experience so
potentially it does that the subtleties
of the difference in system prompt then
could potentially slightly y to your
overall prompt if that was important to
you then I guess for sure which is
something I do find myself doing another
kind of observation about the two is
that Claude is much better at picking up
your intention over a large context
window whereas GPT might get more easily
confused yeah cloud is more able to
follow interesting and and one of the
things I love about Claude projects is
the ability just to upload and refer to
things and when we think about I think
remember be just saying prompts are
disposable yeah and if we take the
opposite of that I guess maybe a
specification or something that you
could upload to a clae project and then
refer to it would you write the two in a
separate style what's maybe the the
prompts are going to be more chat and
interactive based a spec is going to
probably be more I don't know we use the
word canonical here a little bit more
full more descriptive end to endend
what's the style that you have seen in
both short prompting and spec what's the
core differences in language and style
there are a few differences for sure
like conceptually there's o a few things
that are similar which I might touch on
First and this is where the first like
tip comes in I think and something that
we've seen really help us maybe common
knowledge at this point but it's worth
pointing out formatting is important a
theme through this by the way is that
I'm coming to feel that the way that you
communicate with humans is often
directly like translatable to the way
that you should communicate with LM so
formatting your prompt and like when I
say formatting structuring like we
literally use these are not XML
documents but we will tag things I'm
doing this
tag we will tag certain sections and I
think this is exactly how you would
communicate with a person in the sense
that you're not going to give them a
giant wall of text and expect them to
digest it at once you might have a
shorter wall of text that links to a
different wall of text and then that
links to something else which links to a
more foundational document then they can
more process these pieces of information
in a way that works for them instead of
just getting ground in it yeah so that's
something that's similar between prompts
and specs I would say for us as you say
specs are canonical this is a word that
we're throwing around a lot lately
meaning that a section in a spec
directly maps to an output I think
that's kind of how we're coming to think
of it so a section in my spec that says
this function adds two numbers together
that directly maps to the process that
creates this function that adds two
numbers together yeah that makes it
easier to edit it makes it more pointed
it makes it easier for an llm to
understand and for a person to parse and
that's also true also true with a prompt
really I think the major difference here
is that or one of the major differences
is that you'll see slightly more flowery
language in in
prompts specs are technical they're
meant to be quickly and easily
understood yeah well and interestingly
when you talk about the flowery language
there I was like thinking my mind goes
to the autonomy side yeah whereby a
short prompt is something which is
attended and interactive so the output
that you will get you will read you will
look at you'll say yes this is correct
or this is incorrect where so you can
almost afford that more flowery language
and you know verbosity or or almost the
ambiguity a little bit because you're
seeing exactly what what it does back
with the spec you want it to be more
concrete so that there's less ambiguity
even if perhaps you use a prompt to help
you create that spec you want it to be
more clear so that generations of that
specification as an implementation or
something like that is going to be
somewhat consistent I guess they can be
used together as well yeah and I think
the decomposition there is is super
interesting in terms of breaking that
spec down into pieces yeah um I'm
focusing on those pieces one at a time
yeah absolutely during this session then
we're going to jump into a number of
tips you mentioned one briefly there and
these are tips that you've found the
hard way through playing with these
systems trying to get the most that you
can out of an llm the first one's an
interesting one it's one actually that
you wrote in a blog post I'm G to say
last year you talked about task framing
yeah and this is interesting I remember
like learning a lot reading this blog
tell us a little bit about I guess like
the before you go into task framing
actually talk about the steps that leads
up into task framing from having those
constraints at the back end of a prompts
Etc yeah it's born out of me begging my
head against the wall a specific problem
which for me again like we're very much
in the experimentation phase for a while
and I was trying to get llms to make me
certain utility libraries like just
certain functions without using any
external
dependencies now llms are trained on the
internet right and the number of people
who actually write code that way without
using any external dependencies that's a
very low number so I was finding that my
usual prompts God I was and we use the
term the blog post begging please do not
put any external dependencies in this I
swear if you do I'm going to quit just
losing my mind because I was not able to
get the LM to comply so I had a rethink
of it all of my prompts were placing
this external dependency constraint at
the end uh of the prompt which is
interesting if you think about the way
the llms process their prompts they're
reading the instructions sequentially
they're rolling the dice on possible
answers before they get to the end which
I don't think a lot of people fully get
right I think a lot of people think you
take the entire front you pass it to the
llm the llm reads it fully understands
it fully and then starts actually
executing and like you say rolling the
dice on possible answers but you're
saying as it's reading through it's
already trying to form an answer based
on what it's read before it's got to the
end exactly it's waiting possible
answers from word one which is why I
think task framing is important and what
it essentially is it's different from
ordering constraints differently it's
about making your constraints not really
constraints at all just making them part
of the task I use the CSV parser example
in the blog post which is a real one
that I struggled with for a while if I'm
describing a the type of program that I
want a CSV parser and then I say at the
very end please no external dependencies
90% of that prompt is describing a task
where the best possible answer like the
correct answer uses an external
dependency it can be accomplished
without my constraint yeah so by the
time it gets to the constraint and it's
trying to fight this battle between the
path it was going down and the path it
now realizes it needs to go down but the
right answer might already have been
selected like it might already be the
case that's 100% the answer I'm going to
pick so the task framing approach to
this is literally reframing from the
very start write a
self-contained library for CSV parsing
that's a little bit of a simplistic
example of how this was solved but yeah
and that's not about reordering the
constraints you're not you're not
essentially saying at the start don't
use external libraries You're Building
buing the I guess not constraint here
anymore but guidance really yeah
self-contained and perhaps it's
interesting because when we're talking
about this it could actually also be
that those you know the words that we
use because it's more human to like an
interaction to say self-contained and
things like that it may actually be that
by talking almost more humanlike in our
requests it will naturally find more
humanlike examples of of of that request
as well so it might actually even I'm
guessing there who
knows it's interesting but I think it's
it leads the LM on kind of the right
path to start again like the external
dependency thing not actually a
constraint if you frame it this way it's
just the task it's just the task the
task is to write this in a
self-contained way yeah it's not oh by
the way no external dependencies so
that's one example and I found that
really helpful in baking into all of our
prompts what am I trying to accomplish
and how can I make that clear as early
as possible yeah very interesting so TS
framing tip number one number one tip
number two actually now this is an
interesting one when we're talking about
we talked about fine tuning and fine
tuning is really about that kind of like
post training almost to a model whereby
you say here are some example inputs
that you might get here are some example
outputs that I would like to to use if
you get these styles of input and it's
more that fine-tuning for for very
specific cases some people do that some
people choose not to these days and and
like I said with you know Simon last
episode it was very interesting someone
a team that was a power user really a
fine tuning leaning away from that yeah
now your second tip is about how you
give examples to an llm which is so
first of all when we frame that talking
of framing when we frame that how do we
position that next to something like
fine shooting again like the prompt can
grow with you the prompt is a living
document that represents what exactly
you want to get out of the LM fine
tuning is really going to and there's
debate about like how well it works in a
lot of cases like how whether it does or
doesn't get you closer to what you need
but even so like that kind of assumes
that the thing you need from the LM is
static that it's not changing and that
you don't want to evolve it and then if
you do evolve it and you have fine-tuned
on these other sets of examples where
does that leave you basically it leaves
you with a lot of potentially time and
compute wasted but this is why I think
prompting is so magical and it's
I know it's going to sound so silly when
I say it but give examples give examples
of what you mean something I do in
promps a lot is literally describe the
thing I'm looking for and then say good
again like in my XML tags good and then
give it an example of something good bad
and give it an example of something
similar that's bad oftentimes when
people prompt they have an idea of what
it is they want to get out of the LM
like they have a clear picture of what
they want but they're not passing that
information to it it's not an oracle
like it it doesn't know is that kind of
a good thing to have almost as a side
thing that you point the llm to almost
as a oh in this part of the spec over
here is some good and bad examples of
this because I guess we almost come back
to that first one about adding
constraints about what good should look
like when do we put that into a prompt
and things like that yeah I think so but
it doesn't even have to be so structured
in that way an example might be a
verbosity if you want like llms tend
towards more complex more verbose
solutions to things if you want it to be
less verbose you need to give it an
example of what you mean literally give
it an example of a flowery sentence give
it an example of the direct kind of
sentence that you're looking for but
yeah like in terms of specs these
examples are always going to be helpful
it depends they're technically relevant
obviously if you're describing if we
zoom in on code gen for a second if
you're describing a function which you
think there is room for ambiguity or you
think there's like maybe a parameter
that might confuse the LM or something
yes these examples are always going to
be helpful literally do and don't the
same way that you would specify
something for a person if you think
there's room for ambiguity again like
people can't read your minds and llms
can't either yeah no it's very true it's
very true and I think that's it's when
we had a episode of in around the
intercom space which of course was an
area you used to work in previously but
we chatted witho chat with Dez trainer
and part of it was a really interesting
discussion on the short prompting versus
the long prompting in other words you
know you can write a short prompt and
you'll get something back because we can
get something back and because the llm
can fill in the gaps we can actually
write very little in our prompts and
actually get something fairly full back
yeah whereas actually sometimes what we
want to do is we want to write more in
that prompt to get to much more
specifics about what we want and and I
think I think I can't remember the
phrase now but it was something about
the ability to short prompt is robbing
us of that ability to add that detail
and and put our details in and I think
one of your third kind of like tip is
around levels of detail and I think
that's really hard to be able to
understand am I giving too much
information am I not giving enough
information because you still get
something but you can almost get
frustrated with the results what's that
right balance to be able to get the LM
to focus on the right things totally I
think this is so interesting like llms
are so magical in so many ways but then
again you take a step back and these are
their prediction machines yeah and that
can be really helpful and that can also
come and bite you sometimes something
that we saw that was really interesting
I'll describe a kind of of experiment
that we did so we ran a series of these
programs that we described through a
workflow 10 times 10 times each and we
had a series of them that failed like
catastrophically nine out of 10 times
the difference with the one time where
it succeeded often was that the specs
had best detail in them I think that
part of this is you're describing a
problem that the LM has seen a lot of if
you gave it one sentence and you say
again let's take CSV parser for example
if you gave it one sentence write me a
library to make a CSV parser it has the
World opened to it in terms of the
solutions it can pick and if it's free
to pick a solution it thinks is good
then it can follow that solution all the
way through in specs where we put much
much much more detail for these like
common problems common engineering
problems I think sometimes the lm's
getting confused like like we're giving
it most of the information but not quite
and if you think about the choices like
the possible choices getting narrowed
down like a funnel it's like we're
leading it to here and then it's wait a
second but where do I go from here this
only leaves me with so many paths that I
can proceed down does that make sense
it's a a tricky thing that I've been
thinking about recently and I think the
takeaway is think about the problem that
that you're describing and whether it's
likely that the llm has lots of ideas
about how to solve it if it does if you
think that it's likely that it does it
might be the best thing just to let it
go for it and solve it in its own way
but this is very Nation but I thought it
was interesting yeah it's interesting
and I think it's one of those things
where I guess one question is how much
do you care about some of the decisions
it makes about what are the important
choices
yeah that you absolutely have interest
in it going a certain path where are the
other cases where okay maybe you
wouldn't have done it quite that way but
does it matter is it okay for it to do
that and it's I guess focusing on the
detail in the right places yeah exactly
exactly so again CV parser for an
example maybe you don't care exactly how
it's implemented but you care that it's
fast yeah and this comes back to maybe
framing the task I want a super
performant CSV parser that can handle I
don't know 50,000 rows or whatever that
helps and if you don't then follow that
with implementation detail like rigorous
implementation detail that the LM has to
follow I think it's much more likely to
or perhaps perhaps the CSV file is a
million lines long as you're creating it
you actually don't want it all to be in
memory because it would just be too big
so it's like the requirements of
understanding how it's going to be used
which is a bit that the llm doesn't
understand giv it those bits of detail
in all
the a really good point interesting so
let's jump on to the next tip which is
about structuring inputs and I think
we're talking about huge context and
this is interesting now where we're
trying to break this down yeah
structuring inputs being maybe is it
coming from the spec point of view that
you're looking at large specs and you're
trying to understand how to break it
down or was there another angle to how
you were learning at this tip it comes
back to huge context Windows a lot of
people
get a lot out of maxing out their
context windows and I think that's
really cool and I want to learn more
about like how exactly to do that and to
find those useful but in my experience
the bigger the context window the more
chance there is for an llm to get
confused yeah and I found that we have
been binocul against that by breaking
our prompts up this is what I was
talking about before about formatting
instead instead of in line saying you're
going to be provided with user
requirements the user requirements are
this and theer requirements are this and
then I would like you to create I would
like you to write a whatever here are my
requirements of instead of populating
the context this way and again I just
going to come back to task framing I
sound like I'm on I thought you were
going to say CSV PA then yeah I'm on a
press tour for task Framing and CSV
parsing so in instead of doing this
saying something like I'm going to
provide you with these materials yeah
bullet pointing them out I want you to
do this with them and then doing our
fake XML tagging of like user
requirements sluser requirements system
requirements SL system requirements
right this is helpful for the LM again
it's reading these things in a sequence
it knows you've said I'm going to
provide you this material it knows it's
expecting that material and by the time
it reads it it knows what to do you're
not breaking down the requests you're
not saying effectively look I'm going to
make five six seven requests as almost
like a conversation with an this is all
in one prompt but you're effectively
like separating as parts of that one
single prompt you like saying this is
what I'm G to give you this is what I
want you to do this is the output star
that I want you to do in and so forth
but you're breaking it down yeah into
clear segments whether you use XML or
whatever it is it's it's like very
demarcated if that's a work still
outside of transactions so sectioned off
really in yeah exactly exactly and again
comes back to the human element of this
like how would you most efficiently
let's say in this Cen example let's say
that this document was your only way to
communicate with a developer you can't
talk to them after that yeah in theory
if you get this one chance and they need
to understand everything there is to
understand about the task from this
document breaking it up in a way that's
digestible I think gives a human the
best chance of understanding what you
mean and same with the other one yeah
and it's also interesting when we were
talking about the fact that context
could be huge I'm going to show my age
here but back in the day of early
programming where like memory was a real
constraint right and so you had to be
very careful about what you put in
memory when so that you didn't blow the
memory stack that you had here as well
the the rate at which llms are able to
take much greater amount of of context
it was only six months a year ago where
we were like seeing Oh I can't give it
that additional context because I I've
only got a certain number of tokens or
characters whatever as as context that I
need to provide yeah the ability now for
us to just throw huge amounts of context
at an llm isn't actually a great thing
sometimes because it gives us almost too
much of an excuse just to throw as much
context and expect the llm to deal with
it so just because you can give context
doesn't always mean you should totally
100% more context is also more work for
you you need to make sure that it all
makes sense again like I think llms are
pretty good at making reasonable
assumptions a lot of the time but they
can't read your mind and at some point
like these things are going to to get a
little a little confused and when we do
talk about context and like specs if we
look at the longer form specification
style is it better to if we are
referring to pieces of spec or pieces of
whatever it is as context is it better
to break those down into smaller pieces
so that you're only referring to a
specific thing or do you feel like the
llm is capable to almost pick a piece
out of a spec and say oh yeah this is
the piece I care about is it better to
really get more fine grained with the
amount that we provide it that's a great
question always always I would love to
know the answer to that what I can say
about that is we know that there's a lot
of variant when you work with LMS
there's a lot of variants and I think
the bigger your context window the more
you're going to run into variance
meaning if you run the same prompt uh
many times you're going to get slightly
different results yeah and if you're
trying to cut down on variants then
smaller contexts are probably good and
and maybe we're not even talking about
context here but smaller Scopes yeah I
feel like it's fair to say that a big
context means a big scope for the task
that you're trying to accomplish yeah
maybe that's not true maybe it's just
about the scope of the task so when it
comes to specs like again canonical
specs to us that means that pieces of a
spec like directly relate to a
deterministic behavior that we can count
on so a function adds two numbers
together that results in a function
being written that can add two numbers
together yeah a larger like math library
with a huge context describing 30 40 50
utility functions that you want to get
of course you're going to get more
Varian and probably not every function
that you ask for is going to be in the
the final code gen result so smaller
scope equals more slightly more
deterministic behavior from from the El
because I guess you're pointing more to
that kind of like specificity in terms
of yeah this is the thing I this is the
small piece that I want and I'm
providing as context or the the small
thing that I'm asking for there are far
fewer ways of getting that or doing that
in an alternate way so you get that
determinism built in exactly okay we're
down to our our very last a very last
tip and this is an interesting one this
is one actually that when we were
prepping for this you said something
quite interesting and I'm like oh wow
that should be its own tip and this is
around invoking thought processes and
the say function that gets used so tell
us a little bit about the background on
this yeah so again this is something fun
that kind of emerged from our
experimentation phase I think a lot of
people have hopped on to this as well
and I think it's really interesting so
when we talk about
context there's context as in like a
giant prompt that describes the context
of the task that you're trying to
accomplish but there's also context
within a conversation so llms have a
very distinct way of communicating it's
I say something to you and you say
something to me and I capture that
response and I do something with it and
maybe I say more things or maybe you say
more things but it's very like back and
forth and this whole conversation
becomes a context the conversation can
also be the context for the task you're
trying to accomplish so we came up with
this way of invoking and this is pre-
reasoning and I still think works pretty
well as a very primitive reasoning we
came up with a utility function which
just says say it's just say this to the
LM and we throw the response entirely
away we don't care we don't care what
the LM has to say we want to say
something that helps prime it for the
next thing that we're GNA say where we
might capture the response so an example
of this is like I am thinking about the
best way to implement CSV
pars yeah who knew my favorite Library
yeah um what is your I'm G have to pause
you there first of all before we carry
on what is your favorite CSV parcel
today it's the one called CSV parcel oh
is it okay we can continue now my bur
question I'm thinking about the best way
to implement this program maybe you
don't even call out that it's a CSV
right I'm thinking how to write
efficient perform code that is written
like whatever I'm looking for this
particular thing say or I'm looking for
this particular thing are you ready to
I'm G to describe the program that I
want are you ready to think about this
with me yeah and usually what the LM
says is like that sounds like a fun
exercise yes I'm ready we don't care
about that what we care about is that
it's now primed in the scope of this
conversation
for what I send next which is maybe a
description of the CSV parser library
and it's thinking about okay I need to
make this performant I need to make this
efficient I need to write this well so
we found that to be really surprisingly
effective when we were experimenting
yeah H and I think it's like it's
something that I've played with a bit on
my own as well and fun it reminds me a
little bit of the system prompt where
you like you prime it to say hey you're
a senior JavaScript developer who
thrives on detail and blah blah blah but
it's much much more than that isn't it
you're not describing necessarily how
the llm should react you're describing
it's almost like on boarding for the
task it's yeah you're giving it way more
background detail about the specific
task that you're going to ask versus the
way it should respond which is quite
I've not heard of that before actually
it's quite an interesting interesting
rout it is interesting and I think if
you go back to the idea of LMS as
prediction machines that really helps
obviously
there's waiting of possible solutions to
your problem as the prompt is being
processed but at this point a prompt has
already been processed right where we're
populating a context and ensuring that
the probability of certain responses
later is more in line with with what we
asked for initially yeah I think like in
my experience it's very unscientific but
in my experience this works better than
long prompting so having a conversation
feels a little bit mean to say because
we're just throwing away what the llm
wants to say yeah but having a
conversation about the output that
you're looking for and then describing
the task I've found this to be a lot
more effective than just here's 10,000
words on the thing I want you to do
we're obviously in 2025 right now that's
right today is 2025 yep that's cool what
do you think let's take let's push out a
year we're just starting in January 2026
is prompting still going to be an
important thing or is do you feel like
models are G to almost remove going to
improve so much that we're going to rely
less or or rather prompts are going to
provide us with less of a value ad on
top of the the the models reactions as
they come out today yes I think so I
think so to some extent again like it
depends on these companies who own these
models it depends where they want to
take them there's a version of 01 for
example which I'm sure is not called 0an
in 2026 there's a version of it that's
much more capable yeah but still not
opinionated that's a choice that's a
choice to make about the LM which I
think is a valid choice but it means
that you will need to interact with it
differently and there's a version of
Sonet that is just as capable but even
more opinionated or even more biased
towards certain types of answers which
makes it really super effective at other
things so I do think that prompting and
like these specific tips I expect to
become less relevant and less important
like I I really do but I still think you
need to be mindful of like how you're
communicating with this machine in the
way that really works for it you said
something the other day that I loved
which is this idea of mechanical
sympathy which I think is more of an F1
thing like working with the car it was
Martin Thompson that originally came out
with mechanical sympathy and it's yeah
the the example he gave if I give the
mechanical example and you can give the
the LM example the mechanical example
was really he gave about an F1 driver
Formula One driver for example he's
effectively just using a UI he's using
the car he's driving he uses the gearbox
but the knowledge of how that gearbox is
built and how he then knows to get the
most out that gearbox because knowing
when to change at high revs if he's
going slower do I change it a different
way do I skip gears having that
understanding of the mechanics
underneath allows him to get the most
out of it when he's actually driving
that's the mechanical engineering side
from but but the are quite similar right
ex totally I think any system is similar
in the sense that you'll get the most
out of it if you interact with it in the
way that you know it works best yeah and
for now like prompts really are the key
to the lm's heart yeah that that is the
way that you interact with an llm and
it's important to have this level of
mechanical Sympathy for the LM and and
so I think prompting will always be
important in that way but like some of
these tips are definitely a little bit
of cope for the fact that they don't
work perfectly yet then again like the
gearbox has probably changed very
iteratively and very slowly over time
whereas an llm under the covers is right
now rapidly evolving and changing so
it's almost like our knowledge our
mechanical knowledge needs to change
faster and then we change our prompts
based on so it'll probably continually
need tweaking understanding how the
models are changing under the covers
yeah exactly which is interesting
amazing Macy there's been a wealth of
knowledge here from your experience over
the last six months or so at tesle
certainly and Beyond before that yeah
massive thank you for joining us and
sharing your amazing knowledge for for
all those samples very bunch of work in
progress hopefully we'll be back here
next year with some reflection this is
this yearor this year 2025 right yeah
yeah amazing
uh thanks all for tuning in and let us
know if there are other tips and and
best practices that you have uh podcast
at tesla.co uh tell us uh about what you
found most useful if if some of these
are working will work for you um if you
want to catch up with Macy uh Discord is
probably one of the places where you can
have a good old chat so yeah join the AI
native Dev Discord and uh we'll see you
again soon on a future episode thanks
for tuning in
[Music]
[Applause]
thanks for tuning in join us next time
on the AI native Dev brought to you by
Tesla
[Music]